Simon, how long have you lived in Boston?
Simon, 你在波士顿住多久了?
Two and a half years.
两年半了.
Are you enjoying it?
你喜欢这儿吗?
Absolutely.
当然.
Boston's so small and charming and manageable after London.
我觉得波士顿小而迷人, 能应付的.在伦敦住过以后,
It's a big city to me, after growing up in Bunkie, Louisiana.
这里对我来说是个大城市.在我在路易斯安那州的邦基市(Bunkie,Louisiana)长大后
I love the museums here, and art galleries.
我喜爱这里的博物馆, 和艺术馆.
And the beautiful stores.
还有美丽的商店.
And restaurants.
还有饭店.
Well, you can't get my momma's hot cakes in Boston.
Well, 你吃不到我妈妈做的热点心 在波士顿.
Ah, but Boston baked beans and lobster...
Ah, 但波士顿有烤青豆和龙虾...
Right.
那倒也是.
Isn't it a bit strange for you, living in Yankee country?
不会有点奇怪吗,对你来说, 住在洋基队的城市?
Maybe a little.
也许有一点儿.
No stranger than your situation.
不会比你的情况更奇怪.
You didn't win either, remember?
你们也没赢, 记得吗?
True.
是的.
Have you noticed that Boston drivers are quite mad?
你注意到没有, 波士顿的司机们开车很疯狂?
Oh I have. But I can live with that.
Oh I have. 但我还受得了.
Do you know what I really don't like?
你知道我真正不喜欢的是什么吗?
What?
什么?
The freezing winters.
冻死人的冬天.
Ah.
And they're forever going outside in the cold.
而天这么冷他们也总是外出.
Hardy New Englanders, Sharon.
耐冻的新西兰人啊, Sharon.
You'll have to get used to it.
你不得不习惯这些的.